Guide to the Martha Wilson Papers, 1950-2021 (bulk 1964-2006) MSS.175
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Correspondence, 1964-2013
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence
    - Donna and Henry, 1982, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Donofrio, Beverly, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Dormon, Mary, 1990-2005 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Dorothy, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Doug, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Dougherty, Ariel, 1988-2007 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Dowley, Jennifer, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Downing, Emma Elizabeth, 1995-2001 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Dowling, Jane, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Downtown Little League, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - The Drawing Center, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Drew University/ Jim Hala, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Dro and J., 1984 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Dube, Graham, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Dubiel, Alice, 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Dubin, Steven, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Duchscherer, Deb Griffis, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Dunlap, David, 1975-1979 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Dunlap, David, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      Scope and Content
      letter with enclosures
    - Dunlap, David, 1980-1991 (Box 10, Drawer 35)
    - Durkee, Savitri, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - E, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - E + S, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Ear Magazine, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - East Coast Artists, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Eck, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Eckel, Phillip and Anne Scarlatos, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Edgar, Anne, 1983-1986, undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Edmeades, Deborah, 1995-2002, undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Edwards, Bill, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Ehrenberg, Felipe, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Eichman, Shawn, 1990, undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Eidia, Paul, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Eldredge, Letitia, undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Ellen, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Ellen, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Ellen, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Ellen L., undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Elizabeth, undated (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Elizabeth, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Ely, George, 1994-2001 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Ely, Maggie, 1994-2007, undated (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Ely, Rodger, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Em, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - embodiments listserv, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Emma, undated (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Emma, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Emonts, Karen, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Eng, Alvin, 2001-2003, undated (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Ensig Press, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Ensley, Susan, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Envlelopes, 1968-1998, undated (Box 10, Folder 67)
      Envelopes from Series II that could not be matched with their corresponding letters.
    - Enver, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Entin, Alice, 1978-1994, undated (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Enz, Pamela, undated (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Ericka, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Erickson, Jan/ Visual Arts Center of Alaska, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Erin, undated (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Esper, Mark, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Esper, Mark and Lilly Cohen, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Ess, B., 1981 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Essoglou, Tracy, 1995-2000 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Evergreen College/Russell Lidman, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Everybody, 1978-1999 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Everyone, undated (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Ewing, Lauren, 1979-2004, undated (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Experimental Intermedia Foundation/Elaine, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Fair, Scott, undated (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Faris, George, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Fasnacht, Heide, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Fatima, Bercht, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Faust, Gretchen, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Feiring, Alice, undated (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Feldman, Dr. Herbert S., undated (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Feldman, Jeffry, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Fellman, Sandi, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Fellman, Sandi and Shelley Rice, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - Felshin, Nina, 1993-2002 (Box 10, Folder 93)
    - Felton, Barbara, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - Ferguson, Mary, date illegible (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - Fergusson, Claire, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - Fernando, 1979, undated (Box 10, Folder 97)
    - Festa, Angelika, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 98)
    - Festival of East Village Arts, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 99)
    - Feuer, Wendy, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 100)
    - Feuer/ Weybright, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 101)
    - Fichter, Toma, 1979-1985 (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - The Field/ Pele Bauch, 2007-2008 (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - Fifth Avenue Committee, 1994-2000 (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - Fine Arts Council of Florida, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 105)
    - Fingesten, Peter, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - Finley, Karen, 1986-2005 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - Finque, Susan, undated (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Fiol, Suzanne, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - Fischer, Barbara, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Fischer, Ellen, 1992-2007 (Box 10, Folder 111)
    - Fischman, Bernard, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 112)
    - Fisher, Jean, 1994, undated (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - Fisher, Joel, 1990-1994, undated (Box 10, Folder 114)
    - Fishman, Beverly, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 115)
    - Fitzer, Allen/ NYC Taxi Commission, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - Fitzgerald, Michael/ Trinity College, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - Fitzpatrick, Jim/ Washington Project for the Arts, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Flanders, Laura, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - Fleck, John, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - Fleiss, Heidi S., undated (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Fleminger, Susan, undated (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - Flescher, Sharon, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 123)
    - Flournoy, Anne, 1977-Undated (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - Focke, Ann, undated (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - For Your Information, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 126)
    - Ford, Charles Henri, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 127)
    - Forte, Paul, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 128)
    - Forti, Simone, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - Fortun, Martha, undated (Box 10, Folder 130)
    - Fossler, Stephen, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 131)
    - Foundation for Independant Video and Film, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 132)
    - Frances, Jenny, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 133)
    - Frank, 1984, undated (Box 10, Folder 134)
    - Frank, Peter, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 135)
    - The Franklin Furnace Crew, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 136)
    - Franz, Marilyn, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 137)
    - Frattolillo, Rinaldo, undated (Box 10, Folder 138)
    - Frederick, Helen, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 139)
    - Frederickson, Kristen, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 140)
    - Free Shawn and Joe Defense Committee, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 141)
    - Freedom to See, 1992, undated (Box 10, Folder 142)
    - Freine, [Christine], 1999 (Box 10, Folder 143)
    - Freygang-Fladd, Kate and Don, 1989-1997 (Box 10, Folder 144)
    - Fribourg, Nadine/ City Hamlet, undated (Box 10, Folder 145)
    - Friedlaender, Linda, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 146)
    - Friedman, Barbara, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 147)
    - Friedman, Bart and Wendy Alpern Stein, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - Friedman, Ken, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 149)
    - Friedman, Martin, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 150)
    - Friedman, Sabra, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 151)
    - Friend, A, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 152)
    - Friends Hospital, T.B. Ford, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 153)
    - Friends Seminary, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 154)
    - Frigand, Lisa and Marc Westhof, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 155)
    - Frisch, [Norman], 2002-2007 (Box 10, Folder 156)
    - Fritsche, Ed, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 157)
    - Froese, Dieter and Kay Hines, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 158)
    - Fry, Charles, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 159)
    - Fuller, Carole / 911 Media Arts Center, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 160)
    - Fusco, Coco, 1999-2005, undated (Box 10, Folder 161)
    - Fusco, Coco and Guillermo Gomez-Pena, undated (Box 10, Folder 162)
    - GB, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 163)
    - Gagnon, Jean/ National Gallery of Canada, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 164)
    - Gail, undated (Box 10, Folder 165)
    - Gailee, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 166)
    - Galinsky, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 167)
    - Galagher, Betsey, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 168)
    - Galowitz-Ortiz, Lori, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 169)
    - Gampel, Abigail, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 170)
    - Gan, Elaine, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 171)
    - Gannon, Laura, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Gantt, Harvey, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Garce, [Marcia], 1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Garfield, Susan E. / The Rockefellar Foundation, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Garmiany, Adalet, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Gates, Jeff, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Gates, Katherine, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Gatewood, Charles, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Gaulke, Cherie; Mayberry, Sue, 1990-2008 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Gaynor, Mike and Dana, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Gearoid and Cheryl, Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Gearoid and Cheryl, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Gehrig, Cynthia / Jerome Foundation, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Gehrig Family, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - George, Undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - George, B., 1977 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - George School, Undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - George School, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Georgia Southern University, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Gerlovina, Rimma and Valeriy, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - German, Jeffrey, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Gertrude, Undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - The Getty Center / Carla Luna, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Ghani, Mariam, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Giet, Nathalie, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Gilbert, Ame, 2004; Undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Gilbert and George, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Gill, Brenden, Undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Gillies, Archibald / Andy Warhol Foundation, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Gilmor, Jane, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Gina, 1982-1987 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Gimblett, Max, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Gimblett, Max; Kirshenblatt-Gimblett, Barbara, 1990-2005; Undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Glass, Susan, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Gleber, Conrad; Rubini, Gail, 1978-1999; Undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Glen / Glennda Orgasm, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Glenda, Undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Glidden, Joy / D.U.M.B.O., 2005 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - [Gloria], 2003 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Gloria and Empeer, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Glovsky, Alan, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Godine, David R., 1987 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Godsey, Cleo; Brever, Hubertus, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Goldberg, Gary, Undated (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Goldberg, Ian, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Goldberg, Jane, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Goldner, Barbara, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Goldsmith, Caroline; Resnicow, David, 1989; Undated (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Goldstein, Daniel, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Goldstein, Howard, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Goldstein, Malcolm, Undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Gomez, Edward, 1985-2003; Undated (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Gonzalez, Juan, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Gonzalo, Pilar, 2006-2007 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Gordh, Bill, 1982-2001; Undated (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Gordh, Bill; Lewis, Jennifer, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Gornik, April, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Gordon, Loco, 1989-1996 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Gosfield, Annie, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Graham, Dan, 1972-1976, date illegible (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Grandma, undated (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Granet, Illona, 1982-2004, undated (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Granet, Ilona and Susan, undated (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Grantmakers in the Arts, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Graves, Derek Scott, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Gray, John, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Gray, Marion, undated (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Green, Becky/Banff Centre for the Arts, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Green, Denise, undated (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Green, Dor, 1995-2003 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Green, Vanalyne, 1984-2007, undated (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Greenbau, Leslie and Seventeen Magazine, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Greg, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Grey, Alex and Allyson, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Grey, Lydia, undated (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Griffis, Deborah, 1984-1985, undated (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Grimm, Sarah, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - The Grolier Club, 1987-1997 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Grooms, Red, undated (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Grossberg, Shelley Jane/Roundabout Theatre Company, 1985-1996 (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - Grove, Kathy, 1998-2005, undated (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - Grove, Kathy and Larry List, date illegible (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - Grumbach, Pamela R., 1986 (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - Guerilla Girls, various; Materials may be restricted. (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - Guggenheim, Eileen, 1996, undated (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1987-2007 (Box 11, Folder 87)
    - Gulielmetti and Gesmer, P.C., 1998-2003 and undated (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - Gund, Agnes, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - Gus and Jean, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 90)
    - Gustafson, Sharon, undated (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Gutierrez-Solana, Carlos, undated (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - Guzman, Mariano, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - Gylbert, undated (Box 11, Folder 94)
    - HB, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - HG, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 96)
    - Hack, Daniel, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 97)
    - Hagedorn, Jessica and John Woo, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 98)
    - Hagood, Trish, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 99)
    - Hala, James/ Drew University, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 100)
    - Halgunseth, Ellin, 1991-2008 (Box 11, Folder 101)
    - Hall, Matthew, undated (Box 11, Folder 102)
    - Hallerson, Claire/The Builders Association, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 103)
    - Halvorson/Taylor, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 104)
    - Hall, Sam, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 105)
    - Hallett, Joann/NSCAD, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 106)
    - Hallwalls, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 107)
    - Hamburger, Annie, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 108)
    - Hammer, Barbara, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 109)
    - Hampton, Dan, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 110)
    - Hampton, Scott, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 111)
    - Hampton, Sylvia, 2000-2006, undated (Box 11, Folder 112)
    - Handelman, Michelle, 2002-2005 (Box 11, Folder 113)
    - Handlers, Dr. and Mrs., 1987-2003, undated (Box 11, Folder 114)
    - Hanel, Jodi/Exit Art, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 115)
    - Hanes, Robin, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 116)
    - Haney, Theresa, undated (Box 11, Folder 117)
    - Hanlon, Jessica, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 118)
    - Hannah, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 119)
    - Hanon, Geraldine, 1988, undated (Box 11, Folder 120)
    - Hansell, Freya, 1992-1994, undated (Box 11, Folder 121)
    - Hansen, Jan, undated (Box 11, Folder 122)
    - [Har], 1976 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Hara, Tochio, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Hardinger, Ruth and C. Michael Norton, 1998-2002 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Hardy, John, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Harmond, Kyle, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Harnett, Lila, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Harper, Glenn, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Harrington, Wendall, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Harris, Ellen, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Harris, Melissa/Artforum, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Harris, Susan, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Harrison, Marc, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Harrison, Marc (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Harvey, Emily, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Hayden, David, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Heathfield, Adrian, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Heckscher Museum/ Melissa Erb, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Hecht, Laurel, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Hedden, Dee, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Heiden, Stella, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Heiss, Alanna and Fredrick Sherman, 1978-1995, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Heist, Erica and Laura Parnell/Momenta Art, 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Heitner, Marty, 1987-1992, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Helen, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Helen, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - [Helen] and Charles, 2004, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Helena Rubinstein Foundation/ Chelsea Romersa, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Helmes, Su Ann, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Hemenway, Anne, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Henes, Donna, 1976-2001, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Henes, Donna, 1991-2002, undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Henes, Donna and Daile Kaplan, 1990, undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Henry [Story], 1984 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Hensala, Craig, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - [Herb], 1978 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Heresies Magazine, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Herlin, Jean-Nol, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Herman, Shirley, 1987-1994 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Hero, Barbara, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Hewson, Federico, 2001-2007 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Heyward, Julia, 2005-2006, undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Higgins, Diane, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Higgs, Kimball, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - High Performance, undated (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Hijuelos, Joseph, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Hilary, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Hileman, Jayne, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Hill, Leslie and Helen Paris, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Hill, Murray, 1997-2005 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Hillerbrand, Cathy, undated (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - [Him], undated (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Hirano, Michiko, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Hirschy, David and Chris, 1976-1989, undated (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - HO, undated (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Ho, Dennia, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Hodges, Jeanne/NEA, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Hoff, Pat, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Hoffberg, Judy, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Hoffman, Barbara, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Hoffstein, Murray M.D., 1982-1985 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Hogan. Matthew, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Holden, Barry/Prentice and Chan, Ohlhausen LLP, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Holland, DK, undated (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Holland, Sarah, 1984-1987 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Holst, Lisa/ Emerson Gallery, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Holstein, Pieter, 1978-2005, undated (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Holtz, Helmuth, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - [Holzer], 1979 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Honeymoon Miralda Project, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Hoej, Vit, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - Horn, Stuart, undated (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - Horschak, Amy, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - Howard, 1977-1998, undated (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - Howard, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Howard, Barbara, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Howard, David, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - Howland, Rebecca (Becky), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - Hsieh, Teh-Ching and Qin Qin, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - Hsieh, Teh Ching, 1984-2007 (Box 12, Folder 78)
      Poster materials sent by Hsieh can be found in the oversize series.
    - Hsieh, Teh-Ching and Linda Montano, undated (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Hsieh, Teh-Ching and [Maureen], undated (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - Hugh Hefner First Amendment Awards, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Hui, Tammy, undated (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - Huisman, Hetty, undated (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Hunt, Diane, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Hutchins, Alice, 1985-1997 (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Hutchins, Alice and Jack, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - Hwang, Koosil-ja, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - Hydler, Glenda, 1985-2006, undated (Box 12, Folder 89)
    - Hyson, Sharon, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 90)
    - I., undated (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - Alex I [ ], 2002 (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - Ida, undated (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - Ifill, [Natsee], 1984 (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - illegible (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - illegible (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - Imani, undated (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Independent Television Service, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Ingberman, Jeanette/ Exit Art, 1985-2007 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Ingberman, Jeanette and Papo Colo/ Exit Art, 1990, 1998, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Ingrid, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Innocent, Fritz, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Inoue, Yoko, 2007, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Interaction Arts/ Alexander M. Plague, Jr., 1982 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - IRS, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Irina, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Irock, Pansy, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Irwin, Kim, 1994-2005 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Isabel, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Isabel, 1984-2002 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Islip Art Museum, Cohalan, Mary Lou and Catherine Valenza, 1991-1998 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - J., 1996 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - J.C., 1991 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Jack, Elizabeth and Shawn, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Jacks, Robert, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Jackson, Homer, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Jacobs, Gundula and Ted, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Jacobsen, Carol, 1986-1994 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Jacquin, Jeff and Gwen, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Judrunka and Darko, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Jaime, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Jajich, Audrey, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Jakovljevic, Branislav, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - James, Ed, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - James A. Michener Arts Center, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Jon, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Jane, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Jane, undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Janet, 1984, undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Janeway, Michael/NAJP, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Jankovic, Radmila-Iva, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Jarden, Richards, 1976-2007, undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Jarden, Marcia and Richards, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Jardin, Fred, date illegible (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Jaxson, Carrie, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Jean, undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Jeanette, undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Jeannie, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Jeff and Bob, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Jehu, Ron, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Jen and Josh, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Jen/Thundergulch, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Jenness, Morgan, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Jennifer, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Jennifer, undated (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Jenny, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Jenny, undated (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Jerome Foundation, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Jessica, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Jessica and Kerinia, undated (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Jill, undated (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Jill, undated (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Jim, undated (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Uncle Jim and Aunt Marge, undated (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Jimbo, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Jo, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - [Joan and Jolin], undated (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Joanne and Lew, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Joanne, Mike, Meredith and Brian, undated (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Jody, date illegible (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Joe, 2005, undated (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - John, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - John, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - John, undated (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - John, undated (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - John and Susan [Gr...], 1975-1978, undated (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Johnny, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Johnny, undated (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Johnson, Anne, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Johnson, Emma, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - Johnson, Joyce and Marc, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - Johnson, Rhonda, undated (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - Jon, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Jon and Carol, undated (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - Jon and Vernita, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 78)
    - Jones, Amelia, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 79)
    - Jones, Baird, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 80)
    - Jones, Canby, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 81)
    - Jones, Kathy Ann, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 82)